Stewart L. Udall papers, 1950-2010
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Department of the Interior, 1961-1972
  - Department of the Interior, 1967-1968
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Stewart Udall. 1967 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Cabinet. 1967 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, President Johnson. 1967 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Vietnam. 1967 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Miscellaneous. 1967 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. February 1967 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      National Association of Housing & Redevelopment Officials: Dinner honoring Marie C. McGuire, Washington, DC, February 14, 1966
      Harkness Ballet Benefit for Center for Arts of Indian America: Dinner honoring Stewart Udall and wife, River Oaks Country Club, February 16, 1966
      Harkness Benefit Breakfast, Houston, Texas, February 17, 1966
      Ground-breaking for Houston Arboretum and Botanical Garden, Houston, Texas, February 17, 1966
      Stewart Udall’s Party following Harkness Ballet Performance, Houston, Texas, February 17, 1966
      Dinner honoring Vice-President Hubert Humphrey, Phoenix, Arizona, February 21, 1966
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Conference with Ambassador Lukumbuzya of the Republic of Tanzania, Washington, DC. Tape Recording. January 12, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Trip to the Middle East: Plans, Correspondence, Itinerary, Reports, Photos, etc. Includes Tape Recording made in Amman, Jordan. February 2-12, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 3-4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. March 1967 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      National Coal Policy Conference, Washington, DC, March 7, 1967
      Golden Eagle Awards Ceremony, Washington, DC, March 8, 1967
      Oil and Gas Symposium, Washington, DC, March 9, 1967
      Democratic National Committee Panel and Dinner, Washington, DC, March 9, 1967
      President Johnson’s Dinner honoring Governors, White House, March 18, 1967
      White Fellows Dinner, Washington, DC, March 20, 1967
      American Society of Foresters (Washington Section) Luncheon. Special Award to Senator Carl Hayden, Washington, DC, March 22, 1967
      Lunch with Democratic State Chairmen, Washington, DC, March 30, 1966
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Federal Woman’s Award Dinner, Washington, DC. March 7, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. March-April 1967 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      Trip to Puerto Rico and the Virgin Islands, March 31-April 2, 1967
      Lighting of Japanese Lantern, to open the Cherry Blossom Festival, Washington, DC, April 4, 1967
      24th- Y.W.C.A. National Convention, Boston, Massachusetts, April 24, 1967
      28th-29th- Hike along the C. & O. Canal, Washington, DC, April 28-29, 1967
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Visit to NASA Manned Spacecraft Center, Houston, Texas. April 6, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Trip to Arizona. April 17-20, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. May 1967 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      Ribbon cutting Ceremony at Bay Par Sewage Treatment Plant, East Rockaway, Long Island New York, May 3, 1967
      Hudson River Canoe Trip with Robert Kennedy, May 6-7, 1967
      Dedication of Bureau of Reclamation Engineering and Research Center, Denver, Colorado, May 11, 1967
      Dedication of Fort Ward Park, Alexandria, Virginia, May 14, 1967
      Falls Church Village Preservation & Improvement Society and the City Council Design Awards Program, Fall Church,Virginia, May 21, 1967
      Reception honoring Henry H. and Mary Wilson, Washington, DC, May 24, 1967.
      Dedication of Coal-to-Gasoline Pilot Plant, Cresap, West Virginia, May 27, 1967
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Conference on Planned Parenthood-World Population, Denver, Colorado. May 4, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Meeting with Bulgarian Power Delegation, Washington, DC. May 12, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-International Conference on Water for Peace, Washington, DC. Includes Tape Recording of Interview with Stewart Udall. May 23-31, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. June-August 1967 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      Bowling Green State University Commencement, Bowling Green, Ohio, June 4, 1967. See Box 199: Honors & Awards
      Delaware State College Commencement, Dover, Delaware, June 5, 1967. See Box 199: Honors & Awards
      Department of the Interior Convocation Awards, Washington, DC, June 8, 1967
      Meeting with Representatives of the Soap and Detergent Industry, Washington, DC, July 31, 1967
      Swearing-in of Owen Aspinall as Governor of Samoa, Washington, DC, August 1, 1967
      Dedication of Clair Engle Desalting Plant, Chula Vista, California, August 19, 1967
      Inspection Tour of Bureau of Mines projects in Scranton and Wilkes-Barre areas, August 31, 1967
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Float Trip down the Colorado River. June 1967 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of National Water Quality Laboratory, (Duluth, Minnesota) and Tour of proposed Voyageurs National Park Area. August 11, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Democratic Funding-raising Dinner, Cleveland, Ohio. August 28, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. September-October 1967 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      Presentation of Plaque designating Eugene V. Debs Home as a Registered National Landmark. Speech at the Eugene V. Debs Award Dinner honoring A. Philip Randolph, Terre Haute, Indiana, September 23, 1967
      Wreath-laying at Lincoln Memorial by President Diori Hamani of the Republic of Niger, Washington, DC, September 27, 1967.
      Swearing-in Ceremony for Frank Gregg, Federal Chairman of the New England River Basin Commission, Washington, DC, September 29, 1967
      Audubon Society Annul Convention, Atlantic City, New Jersey, September 30, 1967
      Presentation of Plaque designating Georgetown as a National Historic Landmark, Maryland, October 7, 1967
      Inauguration of Dr. Garold D. Holstine as President of Bacone College, Muskogee, Oklahoma, October 8, 1967
      American Association of Nurserymen’s Annual Landscape Awards Luncheon, Washington, DC, October 18, 1967
      Mrs. Perle Mesta’s Reception honoring American Youth Hostel Committee Members, Washington, DC, October 18, 1967
      Midwest Democratic Conference, Rapid City, South Dakota, October 20, 1967
      Wreath-laying at Lincoln Memorial with the President of Mexico, Washington, DC, October 27, 1967
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Conference of State and Federal Water Officials, Denver, Colorado. September 6, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Visit to Cochiti Dam Site and Cochiti Pueblo, New Mexico. September 6, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Industrial Park (Zuni, New Mexico) and Opening of Navajo Tribal Fair, Window Rock, Arizona. September 7, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Hubbell Trading Post National Historic Site, Arizona. September 7, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Memorial Service for Carl Sandburg, Washington, DC, Correspondence. September 17, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Memorial Service for Carl Sandburg, Washington, DC, Program, Photos, Clippings. September 17, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-National Memorial Service for Carl Sandburg, Washington, DC, Tape Recording. September 17, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Canadian Club of Montreal, Canada. October 23, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Theodore Roosevelt Memorial, Theodore Roosevelt Island, Washington, DC. October 27, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. November 1967 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      President Johnson’s Dinner for Nepal dignitaries, White House, November 1, 1967
      Farewell Ceremony for Robert E. Simon, Jr., Reston, Virginia, November 4, 1967
      Dedication of Eastland Gardens Park, Washington, DC, November 14, 1967
      National Audubon Society Dinner, New York City, November 15, 1967. See Box 199: Honors & Awards
      Dedication of Geology Building, University of Texas, Austin, Texas, November 16, 1967
      Convocation Lecture, University of California at Santa Barbara, November 17, 1967
      "Salute to Frank Church" Dinner, Boise, Idaho, November 18, 1967
      Swearing-in of Henry R. Richmond and John F. Baldino as Administrator and Deputy Administrator of the Bonneville Power Administration, Portland, Oregon, November 20, 1967
    - Department of the Interior, 1967: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Opening of Jogging Trails, Washington, DC. November 7, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Signing Ceremony for the Bolsa Island Project, Newport Beach, California. November 20, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Trip to Alaska: regarding Oil Leases and Native Land Claims. November 21-22, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Presentation of Deed of Gettysburg Farm to the United States by the Eisenhowers, Gettysburg, Pennsylvania. November 27, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. December 1967 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      Department of Interior Convocation Awards, December 12, 1967
      Dedication of Phillips Core Chemical Facility, Guayama, Puerto Rico, December 15, 1967
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Department of the Interior Convocation Awards, Washington, DC. December 15, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - Department of the Interior: 1968 Calendar. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Appointment Schedule. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 2-5)
    - Department of the Interior: Travel Accounts: Fiscal Year 1967/68. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior, 1968: Reports to the President. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: "News and Possible News Makers," Memorandum to the President. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President Johnson. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and President's Staff. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Staff (General). 1968 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Staff (James Officer). 1968 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall and Staff (Ira Whitlock). 1968 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Department of the Interior: Jobs, Appointments and Letters of Recommendation. 1968 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Personal and Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1968 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Photographs, Miscellaneous of Stewart Udall and Others. 1968 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Miscellaneous Reports from Various Divisions. 1968 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Press Conferences. 1968 (Box 139, Folder 4-6)
    - Department of the Interior: Cabinet Meetings. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Notes and Comments. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 2-3)
    - Department of the Interior: President’s Special Message to Congress on Indians, "The Forgotten American." March 6, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Briefing Conference with Indian Group and Vice-President Humphrey regarding President’s Special Message on Indians: "The Forgotten American." Tape Recording. March 6, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: President’s Special Message to Congress, "To Renew a Nation." March 8, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Poor People’s Campaign, Correspondence and Clippings. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Poor People’s Campaign, Tape Recording of a Meeting with a Delegation of 100 Indians, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Politics, Stewart Udall Clippings, Correspondence, Miscellaneous. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Politics, Speech Material. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Statement for Helium Centennial Time Capsule. Tape Recording. April 4, 1968 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Interior: Stewart Udall Clippings. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, President Johnson. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Vietnam. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Cabinet and Staff. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Budget Cuts. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Robert F. Kennedy. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Politics. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Clippings, Miscellaneous. 1968 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. January February 1968 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      Trip to Syracuse New York, Meetings at Syracuse University on pollution matters, Speech at Dinner: "A Salute to Jim Hanley"-sponsored by Independent Citizens Committee, January 26, 1968
      Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner: Minneapolis, Minnesota, February 9, 1968
      Salesmen’s Association of the Paper Industry Anniversary Luncheon, New York City, February 20, 1968
      Ceremony Marking the Establishment of Piscataway Park, Accokeek, Maryland, February 22, 1968
      Farewell Dinner for Sutton Jett, Washington, DC, February 23, 1968
      Kansas Democrats Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Topeka, Kansas, February 24, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dedication of Restored Ford’s Theatre, Washington, DC. January 21, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Reopening Performance at Ford’s Theatre, Washington, DC. Includes Letters from Helen Hayes, Abe Fortas, Vice-President Humphrey and Tape Recording. January 30, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 3-4)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Conservation Rally honoring Former Governor Edward T. Breathitt, Louisville, Kentucky. February 13, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interio8: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Dinner for the Governors, White House. February 29, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. March-April 1968 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      Burro Club Luncheon, Washington, DC, March 6, 1968
      Dedication of the Aline McAshan Botanical Hall for Children, Houston, Texas, March 12, 1968
      Wildlife Society Annual Meeting, Houston, Texas, March 12, 1968. See Box 200: Honors & Awards
      President’s Reception for Citizens Advisory Committee for Recreation and Natural Beauty, White House, March 29, 1968
      Dedication of Padre Island National Seashore, Texas, April 8, 1968
      Presentation of Department of the Interior Conservation Service Award to Ansel Adams, Washington, DC, April 16, 1968
      Dedication of the San Luis Dam, Los Banos, California, April 20, 1968
      Arizona Broadcasters Association Meeting, Tucson, Arizona, April 26, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Indian Industries Forum, New York City. March 8, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Explorers Club Meeting, New York City. Tape Recording. March 20, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Interior, 1968: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-"Victory ‘68" Regional Conference for Pennsylvania, Ohio, and Michigan, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Includes Tape Recording. March 22, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. May-June 1968 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      Women’s National Press Club Dinner, Washington, DC, May 6, 1968.
      White House Conference of the Advertising Council, Washington, DC, May 7, 1968
      Dedication of Gateway Arch and Speech to the Open Space Council (St Louis, Missouri) and Helicopter Tour of Lower Meramec Area, May 25, 1968
      Rutgers University Commencement, New Brunswick, New Jersey, May 29, 1968. See Box 200: Honors & Awards
      Institute of American Indian Arts Speech, Santa Fe, New Mexico, June 6, 1968
      Scheduled Commencement Address at the University of Denver. Denver, Colorado. Canceled because of the death of Robert F. Kennedy, June 7, 1968
      Dedication of new power generator, Livingston, New Jersey, June 11, 1968
      "Salvaging the Twentieth Century": Seminar sponsored by Esquire Magazine, on the occasion of its 35th Anniversary Year, June 11, 1968
      Bates College Commencement, Lewiston, Mainem June 28, 1968. See Box 200: Honors & Awards
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Robert F. Kennedy: Death and Requiem Mass at St. Patrick’s Cathedral, New York City. June 6-8, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies. July-August 1968 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      Tree-planting Ceremony, Bryce Park, Washington, DC, July 11, 1968
      University of Utah Commencement, Salt Lake City, Utah August 18, 1968. See Box 200: Honors & Awards
      Family vacation trip to Canyonlands, Jack Currey’s Cataract Canyon Trip, visit to Grand Tetons, etc., August
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies- Trip to Montana and South Dakota: Various Reclamation Projects Ceremonies.: Includes Dedication of Lower Two Medicine Dam (Blackfeet Indian Reservation) and Ground-breaking Ceremonies for Snake Creek Pumping Plant and Garrison Diversion Unit. July 13-14, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Special Presentation to Stewart Udall by President Johnson, Commemorating the Signing of 58 Pieces of Legislation, White House. July 26, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-President Johnson’s Birthday Ceremony with the Cabinet, White House. August 27, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Department of the Interior: Speech, Events & Ceremonies. September 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      Presentation of Department of the Interior Conservation Service Award to Ben Avery, Phoenix, Arizona, September 16, 1968
      Ceremony marking the Birth of the National Jogging Association, Washington, D.C., September 23, 1968
      Signing Ceremony for the Lower Colorado River Basin Bill, White House, September 30, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Speech, Events & Ceremonies-Trip to Arizona, Dedication of the Carl Hayden Visitor Center, Page; Dedication of Hopi Indian Industrial Plant, Winslow; Dedication of Grand Canyon National Park Hospital, Grand Canyon. September 26-27, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Interior: Speech, Events & Ceremonies. October 1968 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      Trip to Wisconsin, and Wolf River Float, October 3, 1968
      Democratic Fund-Raising, Tucson, Arizona, October 10, 1968
      Democratic Fund-Raising, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, October 11, 1968
      Democratic Fund-Raising, Lexington, Kentucky, October 16, 1968
      Dedication of Yellowtail Dam and Bighorn Canyon National Recreation Area, Montana, October 31, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Speech, Events & Ceremonies-Signing Ceremony: Redwoods, North Cascades, Scenic Rivers, National Trails Bills, White House. October 2, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior, 1968: Speech, Events & Ceremonies-Trip to Alaska, Alaska Federation of Natives Meeting and Tundra Time Banquet, Fairbanks; Chamber of Commerce Address, Radio Panel with Native Students at the University of Alaska. Includes Tape Recording. October 5-8, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 5-6)
    - Department of the Interior, 1968: Speech, Events & Ceremonies-Sanford Population and Environment Forum, Stanford University. October 9, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior: Speech, Events & Ceremonies. November-December 1968 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      Ceremony regarding "First Colorado River Water to reach Tucson." Celebration hailing the signing of the Central Arizona Project Bill, Tucson, Arizona, November 8, 1968
      Birthday Remembrance for Robert F. Kennedy, McLean, Virginia, November 20, 1968
      Puerto Rico Manufactures Association Convention, San Juan, Puerto Rico, November 23, 1968. See Box 200: Honors & Awards.
      First Annual Conference on Caribbean Development, Charlotte Amali, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands, November 24-27, 1968
      Christmas Tree Lighting, White House, December 16, 1968
      Dedication of Potomac Heritage Trail, Washington, D.C., December 17, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Speeches, Events, & Ceremonies-Scrapbook of Clippings on the Reopening of Ford’s Theatre, Washington, D.C. See also Box 142. January 30, 1968 (Box 144)
  - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson. 1960-1977
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson and Stewart Udall, Correspondence. 1964-1977 (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Stewart Udall and Oothers Regarding Mrs. Johnson and Projects. 1964-1966 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Dedication of Watts Branch Linear Park, Washington, D.C. May 18, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Presentation of Mexican Playground Equipment to the City, Hains Point, Washington, D.C. March 8, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Ceremony Announcing "Lady Bird Johnson Park," Columbia Island. November 12, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Colorado Blue Spruce Tree-Planting, Washington, D.C. April 19, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      Reception for President’s Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, White House, July 20, 1967
      Ground-breaking for Wolf Trap Cultural Center, Vienna, Virginia, May 22, 1968
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, Clippings and Photographs-Miscellaneous. 1964-1977 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson and the Committee for a More Beautiful Capital, Meetings. March 1965-March 1968 (Box 146, Folder 1-7)
    - Department of the Interior: Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, "Beautification Summary." 1965-1968 (Box 146, Folder 8)